우리, 우리 여자들이 무대를 지배해 (여자들이 지배해)
Do my do my ladies run this ladies run this
♪ Do my do my ladies run this ladies run this ♪
여자들이 지배해
ladies run this
♪ ladies run this ♪
우리, 우리 여자들이 무대를 지배해 (여자들이 지배해)
Do my do my ladies run this ladies run this
♪ Do my do my ladies run this ladies run this ♪
여자들이 지배해
ladies run this
♪ ladies run this ♪
우리, 우리 여자들이 무대를 지배해 (여자들이 지배해)
Do my do my ladies run this ladies run this
♪ Do my do my ladies run this ladies run this ♪
여자들이 지배해
ladies run this
♪ ladies run this ♪
우리, 우리 여자들이 무대를 지배해 (여자들이 지배해)
Do my do my ladies run this ladies run this
♪ Do my do my ladies run this ladies run this ♪
예, 예, 예, 예
Yeah yeah yeah yeah
♪ Yeah yeah yeah yeah ♪
내 친구들 다 멋져, 자기 돈으로 플렉스 해
All of my girls lookin’ good and they got they own money
♪ All of my girls lookin’ good and they got they own money ♪
하고 싶은 대로 해
Pop yo’ shit
♪ Pop yo’ shit ♪
스폰서 따위 필요 없어, 내 돈 내가 벌지
This for my girls with no sponsor they got they own fundin’
♪ This for my girls ♪
♪ With no sponsor they got they own fundin’ ♪
네 얘긴 아니야
Not yo’ shit
♪ Not yo’ shit ♪
도시를 가로질러, 퍼레이드처럼
Run through yo’ city that motorcade
♪ Run through yo’ city that motorcade ♪
내가 등장하면 문이 닫혀
Soon as I enter they close the gate
♪ Soon as I enter they close the gate ♪
대통령급으로 너희 구역을 지나가
Presidential through ya residential
♪ Presidential through ya residential ♪
별거 아냐
Bitch it’s nothing
♪ Bitch it’s nothing ♪
네가 만든 규칙? 필요 없어, 내 스타일 그대로
Said fuck yo rules is the mood damn right
♪ Said fuck yo rules is the mood damn right ♪
내가 등장하면 분위기부터 바꿔
Walk in a room and I set the vibe
♪ Walk in a room and I set the vibe ♪
사진 잘 찍어둬, 오래 남을 테니
Get a pic it’ll last ya long
♪ Get a pic it’ll last ya long ♪
우린 전부 주목받아
Whole team they gassin’ on us
♪ Whole team they gassin’ on us ♪
차트 아래 있는 너한테
You sit too far down on ’em charts
♪ You sit too far down on ’em charts ♪
누가 위인지 물을 필요도 없지
To even ask me who’s in charge
♪ To even ask me who’s in charge ♪
달려,
Ridin’ ’round
♪ Ridin’ ’round ♪
외제 차 타고
Foreign cars
♪ Foreign cars ♪
창문 내리고
Top down
♪ Top down ♪
별들을 바라봐
Starin’ at the stars
♪ Starin’ at the stars ♪
성깔 있어
Attitude
♪ Attitude ♪
괜히 건드리지 마
So don’t start shit
♪ So don’t start shit ♪
큰 그림만 그려,
Big moves
♪ Big moves ♪
난 엑스트라 라지
Only extra large yeah
♪ Only extra large yeah ♪
달려,
Ridin’ ’round
♪ Ridin’ ’round ♪
외제 차 타고
Foreign cars
♪ Foreign cars ♪
외제 차 타고
Top down
♪ Top down ♪
창문 내리고 별들을 바라봐
Starin’ at the stars
♪ Starin’ at the stars ♪
자신감 넘쳐
Attitude
♪ Attitude ♪
그러니 감히 건드리지 마
So don’t start shit
♪ So don’t start shit ♪
우린 크게 움직여
Big moves
♪ Big moves ♪
난 엑스트라 라지
Only extra large yeah
♪ Only extra large yeah ♪
잠깐,
Wait
♪ Wait ♪
무대를 지배하는 게 누구라고?
Do my ladies run this
♪ Do my ladies run this ♪
잠깐,
Wait
♪ Wait ♪
무대를 지배하는 게 누구라고?
Do my ladies run this
♪ Do my ladies run this ♪
잠깐,
Wait
♪ Wait ♪
무대를 지배하는 게 누구라고?
Do my ladies run this
♪ Do my ladies run this ♪
(도치!!!!)
Doechii
♪ Doechii ♪
줘 봐 기
GIMMIE CHI
♪ GIMMIE CHI ♪
줘 봐 바이브
GIMMIE PURR
♪ GIMMIE PURR ♪
줘 봐 눈빛
GIMMIE MEOW
♪ GIMMIE MEOW ♪
줘 봐 널
GIMMIE HER
♪ GIMMIE HER ♪
돈은 쌓여
GIMMIE FUNDS
♪ GIMMIE FUNDS ♪
길은 열어
GIMMIE RIGHTS
♪ GIMMIE RIGHTS ♪
승리는 내 손에
GIMMIE FIGHT
♪ GIMMIE FIGHT ♪
겁은 안 나
GIMMIE NERVE
♪ GIMMIE NERVE ♪
한 판 붙어
GIMMIE CUNT
♪ GIMMIE CUNT ♪
내 무대 내가 씹어 그르르!
LEMME SERVE GRRR
♪ LEMME SERVE GRRR ♪
나갈 땐 박차고, 들어갈 땐 당당히
Lemme out lemme in
♪ Lemme out lemme in ♪
문 따윈 부숴버려
Knock the doors down
♪ Knock the doors down ♪
벤츠 키는 내 손에
Got the keys to the Benz
♪ Got the keys to the Benz ♪
회의실에 앉아 시큰둥해
In the boardroom looking bored cuz
♪ In the boardroom looking bored cuz ♪
난 남자들 눈치 볼 필요 없잖아
I’m not here for pleasing the men
♪ I’m not here for pleasing the men ♪
그들과 타협 볼 생각도 없어
Not here to reason with them
♪ Not here to reason with them ♪
규칙 없이 난 내 길을 가지
Misbehaved miss push my pen
♪ Misbehaved miss push my pen ♪
그들을 위해 나를 바꿀필요없지
I can’t tame my passion for him
♪ I can’t tame my passion for him ♪
경쟁자들 뒤처져, 신경도 안쓰여
Can’t keep up what happened to them
♪ Can’t keep up what happened to them ♪
(우리가 지배해)
(Do my ladies run this)
♪ (Do my ladies run this) ♪
우리는 그들을 압도해
We lapping the men
♪ We lapping the men ♪
이 세계는 우리가 지배해
Top of the food chain
♪ Top of the food chain ♪
새 목걸이 번쩍
Bussin’ a new chain
♪ Bussin’ a new chain ♪
이건 새로운 게 아니야
This ain’t a new thing no sir
♪ This ain’t a new thing no sir ♪
돈은 말도 안 되게 많고
Money on stupid
♪ Money on stupid ♪
어제 탄 차는 이제 구형
Hopped in a new whip
♪ Hopped in a new whip ♪
넌 아직도 내 과거에 있어
You still on my old work
♪ You still on my old work ♪
일해, 일해, 좀 힘들 수도 있어
Work work, this might hurt
♪ Work work, this might hurt ♪
땀에 젖은 티셔츠
I sweat hard
♪ I sweat hard ♪
내 스케일은 엑스트라 라지,
Wet t-shirt
♪ Wet t-shirt ♪
내 스케일은 엑스트라 라지,
Extra large
♪ Extra large ♪
바닥부터 라도 두렵지 않아
Ain’t scared of the dirt
♪ Ain’t scared of the dirt ♪
이미 난 정상
Hit that jackpot
♪ Hit that jackpot ♪
지금 난
Now I’m
♪ Now I’m ♪
도로를 달려,
Ridin’ ’round
♪ Ridin’ ’round ♪
외제 차 타고
Foreign cars
♪ Foreign cars ♪
창문 내리고
Top down
♪ Top down ♪
별들을 바라봐
Starin’ at the stars
♪ Starin’ at the stars ♪
자신감 넘쳐
Attitude
♪ Attitude ♪
그러니 감히 건드리지 마
So don’t start shit
♪ So don’t start shit ♪
우린 크게 움직여
Big moves
♪ Big moves ♪
난 엑스트라 라지
Only extra large yeah
♪ Only extra large yeah ♪
도로를 달려,
Ridin’ ’round
♪ Ridin’ ’round ♪
외제 차 타고
Foreign cars
♪ Foreign cars ♪
창문 내리고
Top down
♪ Top down ♪
별들을 바라봐
♪ Starin’ at the stars ♪
Starin’ at the stars
자신감 넘쳐
Attitude
♪ Attitude ♪
그러니 감히 건드리지 마
So don’t start shit
♪ So don’t start shit ♪
우린 크게 움직여
Big moves
♪ Big moves ♪
난 Extra Large
Only extra large yeah
♪ Only extra large yeah ♪
일해
Work
♪ Work ♪
일해
Work
♪ Work ♪
좀 힘들 수도 있어
This might hurt
♪ This might hurt ♪
땀 흘려
I sweat hard
♪ I sweat hard ♪
젖은 티셔츠
Wet t-shirt
♪ Wet t-shirt ♪
엑스트라 라지,
Extra large
♪ Extra large ♪
어떤 어려움도 두렵지 않아
Ain’t scared of the dirt
♪ Ain’t scared of the dirt ♪
겁 안 나, 난 계속 달려
Scared of the dirt work work
♪ Scared of the dirt work work ♪
일해
Work
♪ Work ♪
일해
Work
♪ Work ♪
좀 힘들 수도 있어
This might hurt
♪ This might hurt ♪
땀 흘려
I sweat hard
♪ I sweat hard ♪
젖은 티셔츠
Wet t-shirt
♪ Wet t-shirt ♪
엑스트라 라지,
Extra large
♪ Extra large ♪
어떤 어려움도 두렵지 않아
Ain’t scared of the dirt
♪ Ain’t scared of the dirt ♪
겁 안 나, 난 계속 달려
Scared of the dirt work work
♪ Scared of the dirt work work ♪
우리, 우리 여자들이 무대를 지배해 (여자들이 지배해)
Do my do my ladies run this ladies run this
♪ Do my do my ladies run this ladies run this ♪
우리, 우리 여자들이 무대를 지배해 (여자들이 지배해)
Do my do my ladies run this ladies run this
♪ Do my do my ladies run this ladies run this ♪
우리, 우리 여자들이 무대를 지배해 (여자들이 지배해)
Do my do my ladies run this ladies run this
♪ Do my do my ladies run this ladies run this ♪
우리, 우리 여자들이 무대를 지배해 (여자들이 지배해)
Do my do my ladies run this ladies run this
♪ Do my do my ladies run this ladies run this ♪